<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Fifth settlement compounds</title>
    <link href="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://vision-Fifth-settlement" />
    <updated>2023-10-02T15:10:33+02:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>abo khalel</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://vision-Fifth-settlement</id>

    <entry>
        <title>sodic 5th settlement</title>
        <author>
            <name>abo khalel</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/sodic-5th-settlement.html"/>
        <id>https://vision-Fifth-settlement/sodic-5th-settlement.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/3/cdbcc7dddfbb19f039c2069bd0cd41a0bd0157c0_9c9dad42336ceef6e96a894f1d05975b1f1cc5b1-1.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2023-10-02T15:10:33+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/3/cdbcc7dddfbb19f039c2069bd0cd41a0bd0157c0_9c9dad42336ceef6e96a894f1d05975b1f1cc5b1-1.jpg" alt="" />
                    Introducing a remarkable residential development that harmoniously blends luxury, convenience, and the beauty of nature: The Estates, a prestigious project crafted by Sodic Developments. Situated in the vibrant city of New Sheikh Zayed City, near the Cairo-Alexandria Desert Road, The Estates provides a serene sanctuary&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/3/cdbcc7dddfbb19f039c2069bd0cd41a0bd0157c0_9c9dad42336ceef6e96a894f1d05975b1f1cc5b1-1.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>Introducing a remarkable residential development that harmoniously blends luxury, convenience, and the beauty of nature: The Estates, a prestigious project crafted by Sodic Developments. Situated in the vibrant city of New Sheikh Zayed City, near the Cairo-Alexandria Desert Road, The Estates provides a serene sanctuary for individuals in search of a refined and upscale lifestyle. In this article, we will delve into the exceptional attributes of The Estates, delve into its diverse range of housing options, and shed light on its flexible and user-friendly payment system.</p>
<h2>An Overview of The Estates Sodic Compound</h2>
<p><br>Situated on a vast 150-acre expanse, The Estates is an impeccably planned residential community that caters to the discerning preferences and needs of homeowners. Boasting a prime location in close proximity to Sphinx International Airport and Sodic West, residents of The Estates enjoy convenient access to essential amenities, schools, healthcare facilities, and major transportation routes sodic compound one of  <a href="https://venues-realestate.com/the-best-compounds-in-new-cairo/">best compounds in 5 th settlement</a> .</p>
<h3><br>Exquisite Residential Units</h3>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/3/East-Town-Sodic-768x406-1.jpg" alt="" width="768" height="406" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/3/responsive/East-Town-Sodic-768x406-1-xs.jpg 300w ,https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/3/responsive/East-Town-Sodic-768x406-1-sm.jpg 480w ,https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/3/responsive/East-Town-Sodic-768x406-1-md.jpg 768w ,https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/3/responsive/East-Town-Sodic-768x406-1-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/3/responsive/East-Town-Sodic-768x406-1-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/3/responsive/East-Town-Sodic-768x406-1-2xl.jpg 1600w"></figure>
<p><br>At The Estates Sodic, a wide selection of luxurious unit types awaits, each thoughtfully designed to accommodate diverse lifestyles and preferences. Whether one desires a spacious villa, an elegant townhouse, or a charming twin house, The Estates has options to suit every taste r.</p>
<h3><br>Villas</h3>
<p><br>The villas at The Estates exemplify architectural grandeur, offering expansive living spaces and lavish finishes. Ranging from 158 to 600 square meters, these villas provide ample room for families of all sizes. Each villa boasts meticulously landscaped gardens, private parking spaces, and access to a range of community amenities.</p>
<h3><br>Townhouses</h3>
<p><br>For those seeking a more compact yet refined living space, the townhouses at The Estates are an ideal choice. These tastefully designed homes feature stylish architecture and well-appointed interiors. With sizes ranging from 158 to 350 square meters, townhouse residents can enjoy a harmonious blend of privacy and community living.</p>
<h3>Twin Houses</h3>
<p><br>The twin houses at The Estates strike a perfect balance between spaciousness and coziness. With areas ranging from 200 to 400 square meters, these homes offer an inviting and comfortable living experience. Each twin house features carefully crafted layouts, top-of-the-line fixtures, and access to an array of recreational facilities.</p>
<h3><br>Luxury and Affordability Combined</h3>
<p><br>A notable aspect of The Estates is its pricing strategy, which ensures that luxury living is attainable for a wide range of homebuyers. With prices starting from 21,333 Egyptian Pounds per square meter and ranging up to 25,388 Egyptian Pounds per square meter, The Estates offers exceptional value for money compared to similar high-end residential compounds in the region.</p>
<h3><br>Flexible Payment System</h3>
<p><br>Recognizing the importance of financial flexibility in realizing the dream of homeownership, The Estates offers a convenient payment system. Prospective buyers can secure their desired property with a downpayment of only 10% of the total unit price. The remaining balance can be paid off over a comfortable period of 6 to 8 years in installments. This flexible payment plan allows homeowners to budget effectively and transform their aspirations of owning a luxurious home into a reality.</p>
<h2>About the developer </h2>
<p>SODIC, a prominent real estate developer in Egypt, has established an impressive portfolio of mixed-use communities in West Cairo, East Cairo, and the North Coast. Since its inception in 1996, SODIC has consistently delivered exceptional developments, garnering recognition and leading the way in creating expansive mixed-use communities in the emerging suburban areas surrounding Cairo.<br><br>SODIC's meticulously planned and spacious developments on both the western and eastern sides of Cairo remain at the forefront of the growing demand for relocations away from the heavily congested central Cairo. The company's projects are renowned for their exceptional quality, innovative design, and unwavering commitment to sustainable development.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>hyde park 5th settlement</title>
        <author>
            <name>abo khalel</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/hyde-park-5th-settlement.html"/>
        <id>https://vision-Fifth-settlement/hyde-park-5th-settlement.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/2/exterior-hyde-park-standalone-villas-new-cairojpeg-1200x900-2-1.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2023-10-02T14:57:43+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/2/exterior-hyde-park-standalone-villas-new-cairojpeg-1200x900-2-1.jpg" alt="" />
                    Are you interested in enhancing your housing experience at Hyde Park New Cairo? Take full advantage of the luxurious and vibrant lifestyle offered, where a wide range of high-end amenities and essential facilities are impeccably provided to meet your immediate needs. Hyde Park New Cairo&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/2/exterior-hyde-park-standalone-villas-new-cairojpeg-1200x900-2-1.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>Are you interested in enhancing your housing experience at Hyde Park New Cairo? Take full advantage of the luxurious and vibrant lifestyle offered, where a wide range of high-end amenities and essential facilities are impeccably provided to meet your immediate needs.<br><br>Hyde Park New Cairo is renowned as one of the most esteemed residential projects in the Fifth Settlement, designed to offer a unique and unparalleled journey. The meticulously curated recreational, commercial, and residential spaces are tailored to fulfill your every requirement.<br><br>Hyde Park Development sets itself apart by offering an array of exceptional facilities. These include a spacious sports club, a well-equipped medical center, a thriving business district, two renowned international schools, a world-class hotel, a variety of dining options, and captivating landscapes that will surely captivate your senses.<br><br>Now is the perfect time to delve deeper into the comprehensive guide that explores the main facilities available at Hyde Park New Cairo Compound, as well as the range of units available for sale</p>
<h2>Hyde park new cairo </h2>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/2/Villa-for-sale-in-hyde-park-1.jpg" alt="" width="780" height="531" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/2/responsive/Villa-for-sale-in-hyde-park-1-xs.jpg 300w ,https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/2/responsive/Villa-for-sale-in-hyde-park-1-sm.jpg 480w ,https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/2/responsive/Villa-for-sale-in-hyde-park-1-md.jpg 768w ,https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/2/responsive/Villa-for-sale-in-hyde-park-1-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/2/responsive/Villa-for-sale-in-hyde-park-1-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/2/responsive/Villa-for-sale-in-hyde-park-1-2xl.jpg 1600w"></figure>
<p>Hyde Park New Cairo has garnered significant attention from property buyers in Egypt due to its strategic location in a prestigious neighborhood on the southern side of N' Teseen Street. The area boasts modern buildings, adding to its appeal.<br><br>One of the major advantages of purchasing a property in Hyde Park New Cairo is its convenient accessibility from the main roads. The middle ring road can be easily reached through the main gates of Hyde Park, providing seamless connectivity.</p>
<h3><br>Here are some notable nearby locations to Hyde Park Compound:</h3>
<p><br><br>Hyde Park New Cairo is in close proximity to well-known compounds such as La Vista City and Zed East compound.<br>The distance between Hyde Park Cairo and Madinety is 12 km.<br>Shorouk City is approximately 15 km away from Hyde Park New Cairo.<br>The compound is conveniently located near the international airport, with a distance of 30 km.<br>Suez Road is about 15 km from Hyde Park New Cairo.<br>The new defense ministry is situated around 8 km away from Hyde Park in the Fifth Settlement.<br>Residents can easily access the regional ring road by driving a distance of 20 km.<br>The advantageous location of Hyde Park New Cairo ensures proximity to various key destinations, making it a sought-after residential choice for many.</p>
<h2><span id="lwptoc5">Types of  Units in Hyde Park New Cairo</span></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.hydeparkdevelopments.com/">Hyde Park</a> New Cairo offers a diverse range of housing choices, catering to the specific preferences of customers. These options include penthouses, villas, townhouses, twin houses, and terrace gardens. The master plan of Hyde Park is highly regarded due to its extensive number of residential units, surpassing 20,000 in total.<br><br>Of significant importance is the wide range of spaces available for each type of unit, allowing buyers to select the one that best suits their individual requirements.</p>
<h2><span id="lwptoc25">The developer of Hyde Park New Cairo</span></h2>
<p>Hyde Park Company, established in 2007 with Emirates Damak and the Egyptian Housing and Development Bank as its main shareholders, has successfully undertaken several prominent projects in Egypt, notably including Hyde Park New Cairo.<br><br>All Hyde Park Development communities share a common vision of creating a harmonious blend of social life, work, and entertainment within a neighborhood that seamlessly integrates urban vibrancy with natural simplicity.<br><br>It is worth mentioning that Hyde Park's investments reached 5 billion at the beginning of 2017, driven by its remarkable achievement of selling all its units within a short period of time.<br><br>As of the end of 2020, the company has sold over 3,800 residential units in the Hyde Park community in the fifth settlement, generating sales worth 2.5 billion EGP.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>water way fifth settlement compound </title>
        <author>
            <name>abo khalel</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/water-way-fifth-settlement-compound.html"/>
        <id>https://vision-Fifth-settlement/water-way-fifth-settlement-compound.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/1/the-water-way-1.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2023-10-02T14:47:05+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/1/the-water-way-1.jpg" alt="" />
                    The Waterway Compound is a highly esteemed residential complex that offers its residents an extravagant and prestigious lifestyle, thanks to its modern architectural design and well-appointed amenities. Living in the Waterway Compound in New Cairo has become a popular choice among buyers seeking a wide&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/1/the-water-way-1.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>The Waterway Compound is a highly esteemed residential complex that offers its residents an extravagant and prestigious lifestyle, thanks to its modern architectural design and well-appointed amenities.<br>Living in the Waterway Compound in New Cairo has become a popular choice among buyers seeking a wide range of residential units available at unbeatable prices and flexible payment plans.<br>If you're ready to secure a promising future for your family, explore the currently available units for sale in Waterway New Cairo.</p>
<h2>water way location </h2>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/1/the-water-way-villa-1.jpg" alt="" width="780" height="520" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/1/responsive/the-water-way-villa-1-xs.jpg 300w ,https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/1/responsive/the-water-way-villa-1-sm.jpg 480w ,https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/1/responsive/the-water-way-villa-1-md.jpg 768w ,https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/1/responsive/the-water-way-villa-1-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/1/responsive/the-water-way-villa-1-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://vision-Fifth-settlement/media/posts/1/responsive/the-water-way-villa-1-2xl.jpg 1600w"></figure>
<p>The Waterway Compound is highly regarded for its prime location, situated near northern N Teseen Street in the Fifth Settlement, with close proximity to Cairo Festival City. This advantageous location establishes a strong connection to the New Capital City, making it an attractive choice for both property buyers and investors.</p>
<h2>The advantage of water way compound</h2>
<p> One of the key advantages of the Waterway Compound in New Cairo is its exceptional accessibility to various essential facilities in the surrounding neighborhood, including educational, governmental, financial, and commercial establishments</p>
<h2>the places near by water way compound </h2>
<p>Noteworthy places near the Waterway Compound include the <a href="https://www.aucegypt.edu/">American University</a>, which is only a 15-minute drive away. Additionally, Nasr City is approximately 20 minutes away from the compound. The location also offers convenient access to both Cairo-Suez Road and Cairo-Sokhna Road. For shopping needs, residents can easily reach the accessible commercial centers of Mostakbal Mall and Wadi Degla Mall.<br><br>The Waterway Compound boasts a substantial land area of 26 Feddan, contributing to its distinction. Residents of the compound enjoy a luxurious living experience with abundant green spaces integrated into a contemporary setting.<br><br>Architecturally, the Waterway in New Cairo showcases remarkable designs that harmonize with the modern lifestyle prevalent in the area.</p>
<p><br>Lastly, the compound features a magnificent artificial lake and charming small fountains, providing residents with picturesque views that enhance the overall appeal of the community.</p>
<h2>The project owner water way compound </h2>
<p>The Waterway Company for development holds the official ownership of the Water Way compound, having established a partnership with a prominent real estate firm called "Equity Company." Equity Company is a subsidiary group of el Swedy Company, known for its achievements in the market. This successful collaboration between Waterway developments and Equity Group has positioned the compound as one of the most prestigious communities in New Cairo. It provides a diverse range of residential options at competitive prices, further enhancing its appeal in the real estate market.</p>
<h2>the prices and payment plans </h2>
<p>The attractive prices of the Waterway New Cairo have motivated many prospective buyers to take a significant step towards securing their future housing experience. For those seeking a luxurious living environment, the opportunity to purchase a unit in the Waterway Compound is highly enticing.<br><br>To provide convenience to its customers, the Waterway development offers two different installment plans:<br><br>The first plan involves a down payment of 30%, along with a 2-year installment period.<br>The second plan requires a down payment of 40% in the second payment, with the remaining cost spread over 4 years.<br>By offering these flexible payment options, the Waterway Compound aims to facilitate the purchasing process and accommodate the diverse financial needs of its customers.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
